

6 Village Green Lane, Apt. 23 Natick, MA 01760

860.268.3956

themikelipson@gmail.com www.mikelipson.com

Summary

Five years experience teaching and providing support in 1-to-1 environments Accomplished creator of technology training and professional development Education Masters degree holder and certified professional educator

Profile

I'm an Instructional Technology specialist, public school teacher, convention speaker, media creator and software developer. I've worked at the forefront of technology in schools, and I want to promote a better, more cohesive user experience.

Experience

Instructional Technology Specialist, Natick High School; Natick, MA – 2010 - 2014

- Taught basic and advanced technology skills in a variety of subject areas
- Acted as a model and coach for colleagues incorporating digital resources
- Designed and administered technology training workshops for teachers
- Worked independently to develop courses and pilot new types of instruction

Game Design Teacher, TEC Online Academy; Dedham, MA - 2013 - 2014

- Taught innovative, student-centered online courses
- Delivered instruction to students using web meeting environments

Technology Teacher, Hopkinton High School; Hopkinton, MA – 2009–2011

- Taught media and technology electives for all skill levels
- Created and taught technology-focused professional development

Education

## Master of Educational Technology, 4.0 GPA

Boise State University; Boise, ID - 2014

Bachelor of Music: Sound Recording Technology, 3.7 GPA

University of Massachusetts Lowell; Lowell, MA - 2008

Presenter Experience

**Convention Speaker**: Education Gamification, PAX East (2013)

Workshop Presenter: Quest-Based Learning, Natick Technology Conference (2010 -

Present)

Workshop Presenter: Using Multimedia Applications in the Classroom, Hopkinton

High School Professional Development (2009)

Leadership Experience Department Representative, Faculty Senate (2013 - 2014)

References Available Upon Request